wowwee.com 2018-11-17

# Privacy

This section explains WowWee’s policy regarding any personal information you might supply to us when you visit this site. 

### Information Collection and Use

Any personal data relating to you will be used and recorded by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may use your personal information to communicate with you, for record keeping purposes, and in aggregate (and therefore anonymously) for market research purposes. You do not need an account to browse http://www.wowwee.com. WowWee collects personal information when you sign up for WowWeeMail email newsletters and/or register a WowWee product. You can edit or delete your WowWee Account information at any time.

### Information Sharing

We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. From time to time we might like to send you offers for goods or services from our company or from trusted partners that we think you may find of interest. If you do not wish to receive this information, do not select these opt-in boxes.

### The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

WowWee recognizes that it is not permitted by law to collect information about people under the age of 13 without proof of parental consent. We therefore choose not to accept website registrations or contact information from anybody who is under the age of 13. You must be 13 years of age to register on our website, in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) & Children's Online Privacy Protection Rule of 2013 (COPPA). DO NOT REGISTER UNLESS YOU ARE AT LEAST 13 YEARS OF AGE.

### Cookies

WowWee may set and access WowWee cookies on your computer.  
Cookies are small text files that a website transfers to a site visitor’s hard disk or browser for added functionality, or for tracking website usage. Most cookies last only through a single session, or visit. None will contain information that will enable anyone to contact you by telephone, email, or postal mail. We do not use cookies to gather personal information such as a person’s name or email address. In order to measure the effectiveness of our online presence, WowWee may use cookies to identify repeat visitors to our site and to determine the path visitors take on our site. Any information gathered by the use of cookies is compiled on an aggregate, anonymous basis.  
Use of cookies is an industry standard and many websites use them. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you can set your web browser to do so, if your browser so permits.

Changes to the Privacy Policy  
WowWee may update this policy.
